SATISH KUMAR PANDA

Personal Details

• Phone : 9348325653

• Email : satishkumarpanda99@gmail.com

· Address: Gurugram, Haryana

Objective

Highly-driven Business Development Executive with ,1 years 2 months of sales experience in the digital and agile environment. Proven ability to identify and develop new growth markets and maintain and grow existing accounts. Exceptional communication skills and ability to navigate client issues through to resolution. Fluent in English and Cantonese.

Experience

JUNIOR ENGINEER (Sale's & service)

2022 - 2023

Rice Lake Weighing Systems India Ltd.

- Identified and targeted key businesses in digital and non-digital sectors resulting in a 25% increase in leads.
- Developed successful go-to-market strategies resulting in a 20% increase in new project wins.
- Managed a portfolio of 20+ existing accounts and expanded business with 15% growth in revenue.
- Collaborated with clients on various projects resulting in 100% client satisfaction rate.
- Expanded personal network and promoted the company by attending industry events.

· Business Development Executive

2023 - Present

SpaceN workspace

- Working with and supporting the Sales Consultants
- Demonstrating high team dynamics and push for better team performance
- Connecting with prospects to understand his/her requirement and suggest him suitable space
- Connecting with space partner to fulfil the prospect's requirement
- Collecting appropriate data and updating the CRM platform and SpaceN Console
- · Achieving the allocated sales target
- Following the sales process/lifecycle diligently and suggesting improvements
- Working on creating reports.

Education

Course / Degree	School / University	Grade / Score	Year
Modern Institute of Technology and Management,/BPUT ODISHA	[B-TECH in Electrical and Electronics Engineering]	75%	2018- 2021
INSTITUTE OF TEXTILE TECHNOLOGY, /SCTE&VT, ODISHA	[DIPLOMA IN Electrical Engineering]	62%	2014- 2017
SHANTI DUTA SASTRIJEE BIDY10thAPITHA, /BSE , ODISHA	10th	61%	2014

Skills

- Prospecting
- · MySQL / EXCEL
- Account Management
- Sales Strategy
- · Client Relationship Management